what exactly is give love well what is
あるものだけでなく 、愛を正確に何を与えています
it yes so give love is a world first vr
それはそうそうそう愛を与えることは世界初のVRです
donation platform and what that means is
寄付プラットフォームとはどういう 意味ですか
that organizations causes charities are
組織が慈善団体を引き起こすことは
able to upload their content in the form
コンテンツをフォーム に アップロードできる
of 360 videos and tell their stories and
360本のビデオのうち、
then end users like yourself and we are
それからあなた自身のようなエンドユーザーと 私たちは
able to go to the oculus app store
オクルス アプリストア に行くことができる
download the app review that content and
その内容をレビューするアプリをダウンロードして
at any time
随時
donate seamlessly through that set wow
すごいそのセットを介してシームレスに寄付
that's that's absolutely amazing so um I
それは本当に素晴らしい です
think you said oculus like what
あなたは何のようなオクルスを言ったと思います
platforms will this be available upon so
プラットフォームはこれで利用可能になるでしょう
our launch platform is the oculus app
私たちの打ち上げプラットフォームはオクルスアプリです
stores gear VR headset so right now
今すぐVR VRヘッドセットを収納
we're considering it to be kind of a
私たちはそれ を 一種の
single user in-home experience but we do
シングルユーザー の在宅体験
have plans in the roadmap to support
ロードマップに サポートの 計画がある
group experiences going forward that's
グループの経験は、 それはです今後
amazing um is it free to download or is
素晴らしいええと、それはダウンロードして無料であるかです
it like a one-time cost or absolutely
それは一度限りの費用または絶対に好きです
free that is absolutely amazing now how
今 では 本当に 無料 です
the heck does somebody like this come up
heckがこのような誰かが出てくるん
with this like whose idea was it to
これは誰の考えだったかの ように
let's change the world by using virtual
仮想使って世界を変更してみましょう
reality like how do you guys come up
どのようにあなたたちは思い付くのですか？
with that idea like it must be crazy
それはクレイジーでなければならないような その考えを持つ
ya know it's a great question so we work
yaは それは 我々が働く それほど 大きな 問題 であることを知っています
with an organization called 3,000 mile
3,000 マイル という組織で
Stoke here and what they do is they fund
ここでストークし、彼らがすることは彼らが資金を提供することです
brain cancer research so years back we
脳腫瘍研究は何年も前に
had developed a Google glass prototype
Googleのガラス製プロトタイプを開発しました
for them that allowed them to keep in
彼らが留まることを許した彼らのために
touch with their donors well while they
彼らはドナーとよく接触
had an event called Race Across America
Race Across Americaというイベントがありました
where the bikers could bike across the
どこ自転車は全体の自転車でし
country and then they would seamlessly
国そしてそれからそれらは継ぎ目なく
be able to receive donations and this
寄付を受け取ることができると、この
was kind of the evolution of that so we
その進化 の一種だったので、私たちは
wanted to know how do we make it easier
我々は それが 簡単に 作るの ですか知りたいと思いました
for people to keep in touch and one of
人々は タッチ との1 に維持するために
the insights that we got from them was
私たちが彼らから得た洞察は、
that there was a time lapse that occurs
発生し た時間の経過があったこと
between the point of impact when someone
インパクト ポイントの間に
feels compelled to donate and the point
寄付を強いられていると感じている点
at which they're actually able to and
彼らが 実際にできるの は
this helped us close that gap that's
これはそのギャップを埋めるのに役立ちました
amazing because today I've been hearing
今日聞いているのですごい
a lot about like kind of like the social
社会 のようなもののようなもの について多くの
impact of ER like things like
のようなERの影響
multiplayer getting more social but to
よりソーシャルになっているマルチプレイヤー
know that you can physically change the
あなたが肉体的に変えることができることを知っている
world now for the better by putting on a
置く ことによってよりよい のために今の世界
head said that's that's pretty darn cool
頭がいいと言った
um that's that's just amazing so like
うーん、 すごくすごいですね
how would an organization get involved
組織はどのように関与するのでしょうか
like this so like if there's like an
こんな感じでこんな感じで
organization that's trying to like look
外観を好きに しようとしている組織
after water or
水の後
would they come to you guys like or do
彼らはあなたのところに来ますか
you go to them or how that work for
あなたは彼らに行くか 、 それがどのよう に機能するの か
these organizations so a little bit of
これらの組織は 少し
both right now
今両方
we're doing some organic outreach some
オーガニックアウトリーチをしています
PR this is actually the first place that
PRこれ は実際には 最初の場所 です
we're demoing right here at VRT OH
VRT OHでデモをしています
so for now it's both if organizations
だから今のところ組織なら
are interested they can reach out to us
彼らは 私たちに 手を差し伸べることができる興味があります
at the primary comm slash give love and
一次通信でスラッシュは愛を与え、
yeah we'd be be happy to talk that's
ええ、私たちは それがだ話を させて いただきたいこと
that's that's amazing are you guys going
それはあなたが行っているのは素晴らしいことです
to give a lot of love out there we're
そこにたくさんの愛を与えるために、私たちはしています
trying to I just do or do not there is
私にしようとしているだけであるかどうかはありません
no try you know - okay thank you so much
いいえ、あなたが知ってみてください- 大丈夫、あなたをとても感謝
your help guys that's that's pretty cool
あなたの助けてみんなクールですね
[Music]
[音楽]
[Applause]
[拍手]